(Sheldon:)Unlike my mole, which is holding
steady at the size of a navy bean.
(Sheldon:)What's next?
(Sheldon:)This is the very copy
(Sheldon:)of The Handbook
of Chemistry and Physics
(Sheldon:)in which I looked up the reaction
rates of mendelevium and....
(Amy:)-And what?
-No.
(Sheldon:)-No, no, no, no.
-What's wrong?
(Sheldon:)I've made a horrible mistake.
(Amy:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)This table,
it's in square centimeters.
I read it as square meters.
(Sheldon:)You know what that means?
(Amy:)That Americans can't handle
the metric system?
(Sheldon:)Amy, I was off by a factor of 10,000.
(Amy:)But the Chinese team
found the element.
(Sheldon:)They shouldn't have.
My calculations were wrong.
(Sheldon:)There must be some resonance between
the elements I didn't know about.
(Amy:)So you just got lucky?
Sheldon Cooper does not get lucky!
(Amy:)You and me both, brother.